<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Geeker&#39;s Way 极客之道</title>
    <link>https://crushlimit.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Geeker&#39;s Way 极客之道</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022-2024 by 极客之道</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 21:02:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://crushlimit.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why Emacs is better than Vim</title>
      <link>https://crushlimit.github.io/posts/emacs-is-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 21:02:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crushlimit.github.io/posts/emacs-is-better/</guid>
      <description>Emacs has unbelievable features for almost unlimited expansion versus Vim. Basically speaking, Vim has lower entry for beginners to easily try how to edit files by a couple of minutes to practice only if you could memorize some fundamental commands. While Emacs will frustrate people without patience then quickly losing courage and curiosity on going on. Emacs is so complicated that would take much more time than the most of people estimate if someone really tries to master it just like driving a car, or more similarity with playing piano - Have fun after long time suffered from practicing until the bright vision comes out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why text editor is so fascinating</title>
      <link>https://crushlimit.github.io/posts/text-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 17:41:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crushlimit.github.io/posts/text-editor/</guid>
      <description>Text editor is an integral part for human beings when carefully articulate the thoughts. People are not like machines that the recording capability depends on the pieces of parts made up of metal and wires but relying on flexible abilities. With the advancement of tools, no matter what operations would be melded into one giant piece - the text editors. Text editor is a trajectory for the reflection of people&amp;rsquo;s thoughts on real world text manipulation situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>看古典 - 聊斋志异的现代启示</title>
      <link>https://crushlimit.github.io/posts/liao-zhai-zhi-qi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 18:11:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crushlimit.github.io/posts/liao-zhai-zhi-qi/</guid>
      <description>蒲松龄是明末清初的作家，传世的《聊斋志异》讲述的是有关鬼狐仙怪的奇闻逸事和寓言故事。构思精巧，文笔生动，叙事状物，人物对话，栩栩如生，跃然纸</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
